{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž","đ"],"osnova":"﻿deter","osnova2":"ent","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž","đ"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"amija","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž","đ"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"em","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž","đ"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"emper","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž","đ"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ep","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž","đ"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"eparac","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž","đ"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"epić","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž","đ"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ez","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž","đ"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ip","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž","đ"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ul","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž","đ"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ungla","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž","đ"],"osnova":"fi","osnova2":"ijski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž","đ"],"osnova":"ho","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž","đ"],"osnova":"kambo","osnova2":"anski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž","đ"],"osnova":"mahara","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž","đ"],"osnova":"mena","osnova2":"er","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž","đ"],"osnova":"mena","osnova2":"erica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž","đ"],"osnova":"mena","osnova2":"eričin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž","đ"],"osnova":"mena","osnova2":"erov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž","đ"],"osnova":"mena","osnova2":"erski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž","đ"],"osnova":"naru","osnova2":"ba","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž","đ"],"osnova":"pan","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž","đ"],"osnova":"patli","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž","đ"],"osnova":"pi","osnova2":"ama","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž","đ"],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"benik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"an","osnova2":"elov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"an","osnova2":"eo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"an","osnova2":"eoski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"arkan","osnova2":"elov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"arkan","osnova2":"eo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"bu","osnova2":"enje","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"doga","osnova2":"aj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"doga","osnova2":"anje","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"doga","osnova2":"ati se","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"dosa","osnova2":"ivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"dovi","osnova2":"enja","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"akovački","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"avao","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"avolak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"avolčev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"avolčić","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"avolčićev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"avolica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"avoličin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"avolov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"avolski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"iha","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"on","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"umbir","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ur","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ur","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"g","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"g","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"gospo","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"gospo","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"gove","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"gra","osnova2":"anin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"gra","osnova2":"evina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"grož","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"gun","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"izme","osnova2":"u","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"iznena","osnova2":"enje","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"iznena","osnova2":"ivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"kra","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"la","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"le","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"ma","osnova2":"arski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"ma","osnova2":"ioničar","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"ma","osnova2":"ioničarev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"ma","osnova2":"ioničarka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"ma","osnova2":"ioničarkin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"ma","osnova2":"ioničarov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"ma","osnova2":"ioničarski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"me","osnova2":"imurski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"me","osnova2":"u","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"me","osnova2":"unarodni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"me","osnova2":"uspremnik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"me","osnova2":"utim","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"novoro","osnova2":"enče","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"odre","osnova2":"en","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"odre","osnova2":"eno","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"odre","osnova2":"ivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"oru","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"poga","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"poro","osnova2":"aj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"posu","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"posu","osnova2":"enica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"posu","osnova2":"ivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"posva","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"preure","osnova2":"ivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"proizvo","osnova2":"ač","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"proizvo","osnova2":"ačica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"proizvo","osnova2":"ačičin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"ra","osnova2":"aona","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"ra","osnova2":"aonica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"ra","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"ri","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"ro","osnova2":".","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"ro","osnova2":"ački","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"ro","osnova2":"ak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"ro","osnova2":"akinja","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"ro","osnova2":"akinjin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"ro","osnova2":"akov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"ro","osnova2":"endan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"ro","osnova2":"endanski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"ro","osnova2":"enje","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"sme","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"sme","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"strojovo","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"su","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"sura","osnova2":"ivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"sva","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"sva","osnova2":"ati se","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"svi","osnova2":"ati se","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"tako","osnova2":"er","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"tu","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"tu","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"tvr","osnova2":"ava","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"ure","osnova2":"aj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"ure","osnova2":"ivač","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"ure","osnova2":"ivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"uspore","osnova2":"ivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"vojvo","osnova2":"anski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"že","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"že","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
